President's Task Force on Priorities and Resources; Records ua010.005
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
President's Task Force on Priorities and Resources Records
1975-1977
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany
ua010.005
2 cubic ft.
Collection is made up of materials related to the recommendations of changes for the University that came from a Task Force created by the president.
Arrangement
Collection is maintained in the order that it was recieved in.
Scope and Contents
The items included in this collection are meeting minutes, departmental evaluations, finance reports, as well as recommendations for University improvements. These documents all proceedings of the Task Force as well as the response by University Administration. This includes a cumulative report published and sent to the President of the University in May of 1975. The report detailed recommendations on admission and curriculum both campus wide and at the department level. They also gave reccomendations on how to follow through on these plans.
Administrative Note
President's Task Force on Priorities and Resources was a group created by the President to work on updating and assessing the University from within. The Task Force was made up of members from each major department of the University. A product of this was the publishing of a report in May of 1975 about their findings related to each individual department.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Full collection was donated to the archive from Arthur Hitchcock, a former memeber of the Task Force.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Curriculum planning; Universities and colleges--Accounting; Universities and colleges--Departments--Evaluation; UAlbany Task Forces & Committees
- Mission Statement, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Mission Statement, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- University Collection, Undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
- EPC + Senate, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Testimony, 1977 September 23 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- EPC Mission Statement, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Report on Unit Response, to Mission Statement, 1976 November (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Finance, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Priorities in other Centers, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
- History, Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Full Report, 1976 January (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Category 3, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Priorities - News Accounts, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- School of Education, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Priorities, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bus- ED, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
- French, Spam, Physics, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Reports- In Numerical Order, Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Select Committee Follow UP, 1975 November-1975 December (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Benezet's Response to Report, 1975 July (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Campus Newspaper on Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Report to President Fields, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Report to President Benezet, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Background Documents, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Committees, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Task Force Support Data, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Task Force Reccomendations, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- School/College/Department Task Force Responses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Non- Academic Task Force Responses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Task Force Responses from Students, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Non-University Task Force Responses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Task Force Responses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Task Force Responses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Task Force Follow Up, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Presidential Task Force on Priorties and Resources, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Task Force Supplemental Material, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Administration and Staffing, Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Task Force Report, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Task Force Worksheets, Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Committee Organization, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Arthur Hitchcock Documents, Undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Full Task Force Report, 1976 February (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Student Newspaper Responses, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Response from Environmental Studies, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Decision Making Process Report, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Report of the President's Task Force on Priorities & Resources, 1976 February 23 (Box 2, Folder 21)